# George A Campa

Jc82200172@gmail.com (520) 661-3054

#### **Objective**

Seeking a responsible and challenging position where my new software coding skills will be fully utilized.

#### **Overview**

· Fluent in Spanish and English · Internet/Web proficient

· Sales experience

· Inventory experience

Trainer of staff
Excellent analytical skills

Quick learner

Windows/Mac/MS office proficient

Strong verbal/interpersonal skills Excellent customer service skills

Multi tasking abilities Organizational skills

#### **Experience**

#### **Desert Diamond Casino and Hotel**

Compensation & Benefits Specialist

09/2016 - Present

- Responsible for the implementation, administration and communication of benefit programs for four casinos.
- Assist with the administration of 401K as well as team member communications, enrollments, audits and compliance.
  - Manage FML and non-FML leaves of absence with reporting and tracking.
  - Monitor the benefit enrollment process into HRIS PeopleSoft and vendor systems.
  - Maintain self-service benefit updates in HRIS system.
  - Manage data extracts to external benefit vendors and troubleshoot issues.
- Analyze financial and statistical data for weekly and monthly reporting to vendors and finance department.
  - Administration and analysis of job description and organizational chart revision.
- Communicate with departments to provide appropriate assistance in the development and revision of job descriptions.

#### **Desert Diamond Casino and Hotel**

Talent Acquisition Specialist

04/2011 - 09/2016

- Manage recruitment efforts for three casinos and hotel.
- Perform specialized technical tasks such as; pre-posting dialogues, first level screening preparation of vacancy announcements and statistical analyses.
- Review and verify incoming and outgoing documentation for completeness, accuracy, and compliance with established policies and procedures.
- Resolve and assist in the resolution of policy-related, process-related, or procedural problems and inquiries received from department representatives, employees or applicants.
  - Knowledgeable in HRIS for PeopleSoft, and HRLogix.
  - Ensure proper updates of job description and changes in HRIS.
  - Provide assistance in the development and revision of job descriptions with Hiring Managers.
  - Conduct research and analysis of job descriptions and pay rates.

#### Afni Inc

**Customer Care Consultant** 

11/2008 - 03/2011

- Attend vendor training to update software system, product knowledge and trained new employees.
  - Took escalated calls when customers would ask for a supervisor.
  - Gather information about customer to place product/service orders to handle their issue.
- Utilize client reference information and computer software to investigate and update activity on customer account.

• Answer incoming telephone calls in a prompt and professional manner. Received up to 80 calls per day.

#### Goodwill Industries of Southern Arizona, Inc.

Human Resources Recruiter 09/2007- 03/2008

- Responsible for all recruitment and staffing needs within the company.
- Using the CARF guidelines, ensured disabled/disadvantaged people got the proper support.
- Knowledgeable with regulations for non-profit standards and reporting.
- Update job descriptions, screen potential candidates, interviewing, extending job offers and notifying selected candidates, new hire paperwork to keep in compliance with state, federal and non-profit law.
  - Enter employees into HRIS ADP, EZ-Labor and entering to E-Verify to comply with I-9 forms.
- Develop, generate, and analyze management reports, which reflect the status of the departments and company needs, along with developing new training methods for hiring and curriculum for training.
- Develop and maintain employee files, and a filing system for the Human Resources department and updated HRIS system.
- Provide advice and guidance to employees on benefits and assists with 403(b) retirement program.
  - Help with reviewing renewal rates for annual benefits.
  - Monitor and coordinate benefit enrollment process for employees with Blue Cross/Blue Shield.
  - Conduct new team member orientation and ensure proper enrollment into HRIS.
  - Assistance in managing internal FMLA leave program.

# **Thrifty Car Rental**

Rental sales agent 02/2007- 09/2007

- Greet customers, complete necessary terms and conditions for rental agreement while using effective sales techniques to encourage customers to utilize service options.
- Maintain and update rental agreement files; contact and notify customers of overdue rental vehicles, inquire as to the expected date of return and rental extensions.
- Balance and count money in drawers, collect overflow of money in drawer during shift, complete deposit slip and place money in safe.
  - Train new employees on computer software, sales methods and company policy and procedures.

## **Labor Finders of AZ**

Branch Manager/Sales Manager 05/2006 – 11/2006

- In charge of overseeing all day-to-day operational functions of office and managing all phases of field operations.
- Responsible for outside and inside sales. Contact clients in person or over the phone in order to ensure quality customer service to both existing and potential clients.
  - Manage diverse staff of up to 150-day laborers and office support staff.
  - Handle recruiting, interviewing and hiring process as requested by clients.
- Dispatch workers to job sites and conducted safety evaluations to ensure that our employees where performing the jobs dispatched to do and to ensure safety measures were followed.
  - Development of opportunities by selling to clients and developing prospective clients.
- Collection duties include: accounts receivable, follow-up on past due accounts, outside collection referrals, payment posting and credit requests.
- Accounts payables duties include: issuing paychecks to workers on a daily basis, verifying hours worked with customers.
- Human Resources duties include payroll, internal staffing, new hire orientation, compensation/ benefits, employee relations, unemployment, FMLA, workers compensation, record keeping, description changes and analyzing job market.

#### **Volt Technical Resources**

- Responsible for the recruiting, interviewing and hiring of candidates for the US western and southwest region.
  - Contact clients in person or over the phone in order to ensure client satisfaction and retention.
  - Develop and maintain business relationships with prospective clients within the Tucson region.
- Accounts included Fortune 500 companies from varied business sectors including IT, Medical, Industrial, Scientific, Military and Telecommunication Industries.
  - Market candidates and the company, and quoting mark-up rates.
  - Responsible for direct sales in the Tucson region.
  - Marketing most marketable candidates to new perspective clients and quoting direct hire rates.
  - Network with all available resources.
  - Utilize the Internet for research and outside the box recruiting.
  - Provide advice and guidance to contact employees on benefits and assists with 401(k)

# Retirement Program.

Conduct research and analysis of job descriptions and pay rates.

#### Aerotek

Sourcing Specialist/On-Premise Manager 04/2005 – 08/2005

- Recruit and source for Commercial Staffing, Commercial Engineering and Environmental Engineering clients including interviewing candidates and ensuring that all their skills were identified.
  - Assure total customer satisfaction by handling all inquiries and resolving problems.
  - Interact with managers and employees at all levels.
  - Review company policies and procedures with applicants.
  - Behavior Based Interviewing.
- Took accurate job descriptions from clients and matching qualified candidates in their technical organization.
- Responsible for the hiring, training and mentoring of the manufacturing team, this included reviewing resumes, conducting interviews, training and retraining on current and new standards of business.
  - Responsible for managing 30-45 manufacturing contracted employees at a client facility.
  - Coordinate and schedule contracted employees to keep production high.
- Human Resource duties included ensuring proper completion of application documents to the standards of Federal and State regulations, administration of the 401(k) plan including team member communications, enrollments, audits, compliance, and documentation. Monitored and coordinated the benefit enrollment process for all contract employees, conducts new employees orientation.
- Account Payable duties include issuing paychecks to workers on a weekly basis by verifying hours worked through client database.
- Dealing with disciplinary measures such as write-ups, suspensions, lay offs and terminations of employees as needed.

## **Education**

## **University of Arizona Coding Bootcamp**

Completion November 2019

## **Pima Community College**

Associate of Business Administration (6 Semesters Completed)

## **Amphitheater High School**

High School Diploma